newslo.com 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy - Newslo

**NEWSLO Privacy Policy (Last updated 5/23/2014 )**

At Newslo we are committed to protecting the privacy, accuracy and reliability of any personal information you choose to provide and to safeguarding such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. This Privacy Policy applies to those websites that are part of Newslo.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back often. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by sending an e-mail message to ag@newslo.com.

**Collection of Personal Information**

You do not need to provide any information that identifies you (“personal information”) to use a Newslo.com. In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information.

However, if you want to use certain online services, you may be asked to provide some personal information, such as your name, facebook account or e-mail address. We also may ask you to choose a user name and password and provide that information when accessing certain online features. If you do not want to give us any personal information, you can always decide not to use the services. The choice is yours. We are only interested in offering you convenient online services that match your interests and needs.

Some examples of when we may request personal information include the following:

E-News. You can register to receive notifications and newsletters from Newslo.com. In order to provide you with these e-mail notifications, we may ask you to provide certain personal information, such as your name and e-mail address.

Comments/Questions. You may send us comments or questions about your use of the site. You need not identify yourself to send a comment or question, but we may collect your e-mail address so that we can send you a response. If you choose to provide other personal information in your comment or question, we may keep it in our correspondence files.

The above list contains some of the instances when Newslo.com may collect your personal information. Please note that many of our websites may offer additional online features and services and may ask you to provide some personal information before permitting you to access those areas. This Privacy Policy governs the collection of any personal information you provide to Newslo.com

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

Newslo.com uses your personal information for three general purposes. First, we use the information to provide you with the services you request and to respond to billing and/or other questions related to such service offerings. Second, we use the information to understand your use of our websites and to notify you about updates to our sites or to send you marketing materials or promotional offers that may be of interest. Third, we may use this information in aggregate form to help us evaluate and modify existing services and to help us develop additional services that are likely to be of interest to our users.

We may share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties in limited instances. For example, we may share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties as is necessary to process or collect payments, or service registered-user accounts. We also may hire third-party technology providers to host the WKTV Television websites and

We may also share aggregate, non-personal information about website usage with unaffiliated third parties, including, but not limited to, government agencies, advertisers and the media. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information about our users.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Newslo.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to Newslo in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to Newslo.com our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by advertising companies, please send an e-mail to ag@Newslo.com.

Finally, we may be required to disclose personal information by law or legal process, to protect and defend the rights or property of Newslo.com, or to protect the personal safety of users to one of our sites. We also reserve the right to contact appropriate authorities when activities that are illegal or violate our policies are taking place on Newslo.com.

Except under the limited circumstances described above, we will not disclose any of your personal information to unaffiliated third parties.

**External Links**

Newslo may provide links to various websites. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred from Newslo and connected to the website of the organization or company that you selected. Even if an affiliation exists between Newslo and a third-party website, Newslo exercises no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a website that is linked to a Newslo site, you should consult that site’s Privacy Policy before providing those sites with any of your personal information.

**Terms, Changes and Questions**

By using Newslo.com, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use or disclose any personal information through one of our sites.

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

If you have any questions or comments about this policy or our use of personal information, you may send an e-mail to ag@newslo.com.

We will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of personal information.

How we use cookies

Our website uses cookies. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

About cookies

Cookies consist of pieces of text, often including unique identifiers, that are sent by web servers to web browsers, and which may then be sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and to identify users returning to a website.

Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

Cookies on this website

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies on this website.

We will send to you the following cookies:

Google Analytics (persistent cookie)  
How we use cookies

Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes:

To recognise your computer when you visit our website;  
To track you as you navigate our website;  
To improve the website’s usability;  
To analyse the use of our website.  
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

Blocking cookies

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. For example:

in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector;  
in Firefox you can block all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Options”, and un-checking “Accept cookies from sites” in the “Privacy” box.  
Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

Deleting cookies

You can also delete cookies already stored on your computer:

in Internet Explorer, you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835);  
in Firefox, you can delete cookies by, first ensuring that cookies are to be deleted when you “clear private data” (this setting can be changed by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Settings” in the “Private Data” box) and then clicking “Clear private data” in the “Tools” menu.  
Obviously, doing this may have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.

Contact us

This website is owned and operated by Wnets.

If you have any questions about our cookies or this cookies policy, please contact us.
